451.7633, 1621.9839, 1001.4982

OBJECT - 2894
456.6567, 1615.7222, 1001.0886 // Flying book 1
454.4325, 1616.5439, 1001.0886 // Flying book 2

Quiz metal:
1. Before starting to work with a metal, what should you do?
* Operating the metal.
* Marking out the metal.
* Heating the metal.
* Combining the metal.

2. What's the name of the tool that measure the distance between two points?
* Length meter.
* Clippers.
* Calipers.
* Lengher.

3. How accurate the tool of measurement?
* 24.2 micro meter.
* 12.7 micro meter.
* 25.4 micro meter.
* 31.6 micro meter.

4. What would you do after you finished the layout?
* Begin drawing. 
* Begin heating the metal.
* Begin cutting/drilling.
* Begin applying oil.

Metalworking generally is divided into the following categories, forming, cutting, and, joining.\nEach of these categories contain various processes.\nPrior to most operations, the metal must be marked out and/or measured, depending on the desired finished product.\nMarking out (also known as layout) is the process of transferring a design or pattern to a workpiece and is the first step in the handcraft of metalworking.\nMost calipers have two sets of flat, parallel edges used for inner or outer diameter measurements. These calipers can be accurate to within one-thousandth of an inch (25.4 mic-m). Different types of calipers have different mechanisms for displaying the distance measured.\nCutting is a collection of processes wherein material is brought to a specified geometry by removing excess material using various kinds of tooling to leave a finished part that meets specifications. The net result of cutting is two products, the waste or excess material, and the finished part.

Different types of calipers have different mechanisms for displaying the distance measured.\nCutting is a collection of processes wherein material is brought to a specified geometry by removing excess material using various kinds of tooling to leave a finished part that meets specifications. The net result of cutting is two products, the waste or excess material, and the finished part.
